var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "فَأَتَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "so came upon them",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "fa-atāhumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيهِ",
        "answer": "will come",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "yatīhi",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَكُمُ",
        "answer": "comes to you",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "yatiyakumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِيَكُمُ",
        "answer": "comes to you",
        "pcklId": "220",
        "tlit": "yatiyakumu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "come to you",
        "pcklId": "221",
        "tlit": "yatikum",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوتِيتُهُ",
        "answer": "I have been given it",
        "pcklId": "488",
        "tlit": "ūtītuhu",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their reward",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "ajrahum",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their due",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "ajrahum",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجْرُ",
        "answer": "(is the) reward",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "ajru",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأَجَلٍ",
        "answer": "for a term",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "li-ajalin",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَجَلٍ",
        "answer": "a term",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ajalin",
        "frequency": "56",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "240",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّخِذَ",
        "answer": "take",
        "pcklId": "241",
        "tlit": "yattakhidha",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّخَذُوا",
        "answer": "have they taken",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "ittakhadhū",
        "frequency": "273",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةَ",
        "answer": "the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirata",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "l-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْآخِرَةِ",
        "answer": "in the Hereafter",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "bil-ākhirati",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "(of) another",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "the others",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "l-ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "a second time",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذْ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "204",
        "tlit": "idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذَا",
        "answer": "and when",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "wa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "behold",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "So when",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَإِذَا",
        "answer": "and behold",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "fa-idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": "409",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "339",
        "tlit": "wa-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "340",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "341",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "342",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "343",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "344",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "and the earth",
        "pcklId": "345",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "while the earth",
        "pcklId": "346",
        "tlit": "wal-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "347",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "348",
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضَ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "349",
        "tlit": "l-arḍa",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "447",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "448",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَّا",
        "answer": "except",
        "pcklId": "449",
        "tlit": "illā",
        "frequency": "663",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1056",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1057",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "and those who",
        "pcklId": "1058",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "[those] who",
        "pcklId": "1059",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "For those who",
        "pcklId": "1060",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) those who",
        "pcklId": "1061",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1062",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "1063",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(are) they whom",
        "pcklId": "1064",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1065",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "1066",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1067",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِي",
        "answer": "And the one who",
        "pcklId": "1068",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(of) what",
        "pcklId": "1069",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(of) what",
        "pcklId": "1070",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "with those",
        "pcklId": "1071",
        "tlit": "bi-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّتِي",
        "answer": "and the one who",
        "pcklId": "1072",
        "tlit": "wa-allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّتِي",
        "answer": "the one whom",
        "pcklId": "1073",
        "tlit": "allatī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who",
        "pcklId": "1074",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those",
        "pcklId": "1075",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1076",
        "tlit": "lilladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those",
        "pcklId": "1077",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1078",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "1079",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1080",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1081",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "And those who",
        "pcklId": "1082",
        "tlit": "wa-alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1083",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1084",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1085",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "Who",
        "pcklId": "1086",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَٰهَ",
        "answer": "god",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "ilāha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2264",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2265",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "for Allah",
        "pcklId": "2266",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2267",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2268",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2269",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah (had) intended",
        "pcklId": "2270",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2271",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(is) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2272",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2273",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "to Allah",
        "pcklId": "2274",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2275",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2276",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "I worship Allah",
        "pcklId": "2277",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2278",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2279",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has guided them",
        "pcklId": "2280",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2281",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah fails",
        "pcklId": "2282",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2283",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah has expanded",
        "pcklId": "2284",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(the) remembrance of Allah",
        "pcklId": "2285",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2286",
        "tlit": "al-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2287",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2288",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah lets go astray",
        "pcklId": "2289",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "So Allah made them",
        "pcklId": "2290",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah sets forth",
        "pcklId": "2291",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(be) to Allah",
        "pcklId": "2292",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2293",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "That Allah will remove",
        "pcklId": "2294",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2295",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah lets go astray ",
        "pcklId": "2296",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah guides",
        "pcklId": "2297",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2298",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2299",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2300",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah intended for me",
        "pcklId": "2301",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Sufficient (is) Allah for me",
        "pcklId": "2302",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2303",
        "tlit": "al-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2304",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "To Allah (belongs)",
        "pcklId": "2305",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah is mentioned",
        "pcklId": "2306",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2307",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2308",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2309",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2310",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2311",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2312",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2313",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah will deliver",
        "pcklId": "2314",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2315",
        "tlit": "al-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2316",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2317",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "But worship Allah",
        "pcklId": "2318",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2319",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "Allah wills",
        "pcklId": "2320",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(be) to Allah",
        "pcklId": "2321",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "to Allah",
        "pcklId": "2322",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُمَّ",
        "answer": "O Allah",
        "pcklId": "2850",
        "tlit": "l-lahuma",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "571",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "572",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "573",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to Him",
        "pcklId": "574",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "[to] Him",
        "pcklId": "575",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "576",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "at",
        "pcklId": "577",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "578",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْهِ",
        "answer": "to Him",
        "pcklId": "579",
        "tlit": "ilayhi",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "580",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "581",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكَ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "582",
        "tlit": "ilayka",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِلَى",
        "answer": "and to",
        "pcklId": "583",
        "tlit": "wa-ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَىٰ",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "584",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "585",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمَّنْ",
        "answer": "Is (one) who",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "amman",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَمِ",
        "answer": "Or",
        "pcklId": "83",
        "tlit": "ami",
        "frequency": "137",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمِرْتُ",
        "answer": "[I] am commanded",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "umir'tu",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُمِرْتُ",
        "answer": "And I am commanded",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "wa-umir'tu",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَأْمُرُونِّي",
        "answer": "you order me",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "tamurūnnī",
        "frequency": "248",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُمَّهَاتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "(of) your mothers",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ummahātikum",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "431",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "432",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "who believe",
        "pcklId": "433",
        "tlit": "yu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانَ",
        "answer": "[the] man",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "l-insāna",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانَ",
        "answer": "[the] man",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "l-insāna",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَنَّىٰ",
        "answer": "Then how",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "fa-annā",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "آنَاءَ",
        "answer": "(during) hours",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ānāa",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَهْلِيهِمْ",
        "answer": "and their families",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "wa-ahlīhim",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوَّلَ",
        "answer": "(the) first",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "awwala",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُولُو",
        "answer": "those of understanding",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "ulū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُولُو",
        "answer": "the men of understanding",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "ulū",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِأُولِي",
        "answer": "for those of understanding",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "li-ulī",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآيَاتٍ",
        "answer": "surely (are) signs",
        "pcklId": "314",
        "tlit": "laāyātin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَآيَاتٍ",
        "answer": "surely (are) signs",
        "pcklId": "315",
        "tlit": "laāyātin",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِي",
        "answer": "My Verses",
        "pcklId": "316",
        "tlit": "āyātī",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِآيَاتِ",
        "answer": "in (the) Verses",
        "pcklId": "317",
        "tlit": "biāyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "آيَاتِ",
        "answer": "(the) Verses",
        "pcklId": "318",
        "tlit": "āyāti",
        "frequency": "382",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبِئْسَ",
        "answer": "and wretched is",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "fabi'sa",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَدَا",
        "answer": "And (will) appear",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "wabadā",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَدَا",
        "answer": "And will become apparent",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "wabadā",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَبْسُطُ",
        "answer": "extends",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "yabsuṭu",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَبَشِّرْ",
        "answer": "So give glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "fabashir",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَبْشِرُونَ",
        "answer": "rejoice",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "yastabshirūna",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْبُشْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "(are) glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "l-bush'rā",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُطُونِ",
        "answer": "(the) wombs",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "buṭūni",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِ",
        "answer": "after",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "baʿdi",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَغْتَةً",
        "answer": "suddenly",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "baghtatan",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَبْنِيَّةٌ",
        "answer": "built high",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "mabniyyatun",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَتَبَوَّأُ",
        "answer": "we may settle",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "natabawwa-u",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْوَابُهَا",
        "answer": "its gates",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "abwābuhā",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْوَابَ",
        "answer": "(the) gates",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "abwāba",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَبْوَابُهَا",
        "answer": "its gates",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "abwābuhā",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "242",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "between",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَهُمْ",
        "answer": "between them",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "baynahum",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٍ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "456",
        "tlit": "mubīnin",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُبِينُ",
        "answer": "the clear",
        "pcklId": "511",
        "tlit": "l-mubīnu",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيَتَّبِعُونَ",
        "answer": "then follow",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "fayattabiʿūna",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاتَّبِعُوا",
        "answer": "And follow",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "wa-ittabiʿū",
        "frequency": "172",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "below them",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "taḥtihim",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "beneath it",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتْلُونَ",
        "answer": "reciting",
        "pcklId": "49",
        "tlit": "yatlūna",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَلَاثٍ",
        "answer": "three",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "thalāthin",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "ثَمَانِيَةَ",
        "answer": "eight",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "thamāniyata",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَانِيَ",
        "answer": "oft-repeated",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "mathāniya",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثْوًى",
        "answer": "an abode",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "mathwan",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثْوًى",
        "answer": "an abode",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "mathwan",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثْوَى",
        "answer": "(the) abode",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "mathwā",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْرِي",
        "answer": "running",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "yajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flow",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَجْزِيَهُمْ",
        "answer": "and reward them",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "wayajziyahum",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَزَاءُ",
        "answer": "(is the) reward",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "jazāu",
        "frequency": "118",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَعَلَ",
        "answer": "He made",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "jaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجَعَلَ",
        "answer": "and he sets up",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "wajaʿala",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَجْعَلُهُ",
        "answer": "He makes them",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "yajʿaluhu",
        "frequency": "346",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُلُودُ",
        "answer": "(the) skins",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "julūdu",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "جُلُودُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their skins",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "julūduhum",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَمِيعًا",
        "answer": "entirely",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "jamīʿan",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "اجْتَنَبُوا",
        "answer": "avoid",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ij'tanabū",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنْبِ",
        "answer": "regard (to)",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "janbi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "Paradise",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَنَّةِ",
        "answer": "(in) Paradise",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "l-janati",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْجَاهِلُونَ",
        "answer": "ignorant ones",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-jāhilūna",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُ",
        "answer": "it comes to him",
        "pcklId": "214",
        "tlit": "jāahu",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَ",
        "answer": "brought",
        "pcklId": "215",
        "tlit": "jāa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَتْكَ",
        "answer": "came to you",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "jāatka",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَجِيءَ",
        "answer": "and (will) be brought",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "wajīa",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءُوهَا",
        "answer": "they reach it",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "jāūhā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءُوهَا",
        "answer": "they reach it",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "jāūhā",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَحْبَطَنَّ",
        "answer": "surely, will become worthless",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "layaḥbaṭanna",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَدِيثِ",
        "answer": "(of) [the] statement ",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-ḥadīthi",
        "frequency": "36",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْذَرُ",
        "answer": "fearing",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "yaḥdharu",
        "frequency": "21",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْزَنُونَ",
        "answer": "will grieve",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "yaḥzanūna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْتَسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "taken into account",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "yaḥtasibūna",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسْبِيَ",
        "answer": "Sufficient (is) Allah for me",
        "pcklId": "58",
        "tlit": "ḥasbiya",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِسَابٍ",
        "answer": "account",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "ḥisābin",
        "frequency": "109",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا حَسْرَتَا",
        "answer": "Oh! My regret",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "yāḥasratā",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنُوا",
        "answer": "do good",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "aḥsanū",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنَهُ",
        "answer": "the best thereof",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "aḥsanahu",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنَ",
        "answer": "(the) best",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "aḥsana",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَحْسَنِ",
        "answer": "for (the) best",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "bi-aḥsani",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَحْسَنَ",
        "answer": "(the) best",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "aḥsana",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَسَنَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) good",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "ḥasanatun",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُحْسِنِينَ",
        "answer": "the good-doers",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "l-muḥ'sinīna",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "حُطَامًا",
        "answer": "debris",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥuṭāman",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَافِّينَ",
        "answer": "surrounding",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ḥāffīna",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقَّ",
        "answer": "became due",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقَّتْ",
        "answer": "has been justified",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqat",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in truth",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in [the] truth",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in truth",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَقَّ",
        "answer": "(with) true",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "ḥaqqa",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in truth",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "in truth",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "bil-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحْكُمُ",
        "answer": "will judge",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "yaḥkumu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْكُمُ",
        "answer": "will judge",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "taḥkumu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمِ",
        "answer": "the All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmi",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَحِلُّ",
        "answer": "and descends",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wayaḥillu",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَمْدُ",
        "answer": "All praise",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "l-ḥamdu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَمْدُ",
        "answer": "All praise",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-ḥamdu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِحَمْدِ",
        "answer": "(the) praise",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "biḥamdi",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَمْدُ",
        "answer": "All praise be",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "l-ḥamdu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَوْلِ",
        "answer": "around",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "ḥawli",
        "frequency": "25",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "where",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "حَيْثُ",
        "answer": "wherever",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "ḥaythu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحَاقَ",
        "answer": "and will surround",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "waḥāqa",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينَ",
        "answer": "(at the) time",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "ḥīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "حِينَ",
        "answer": "when",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "ḥīna",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَيَاةِ",
        "answer": "the life",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "l-ḥayati",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْرِجُ",
        "answer": "He produces",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "yukh'riju",
        "frequency": "182",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَزَنَتُهَا",
        "answer": "its keepers",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "khazanatuhā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَزَنَتُهَا",
        "answer": "its keepers",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "khazanatuhā",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْزِيهِ",
        "answer": "disgracing him",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "yukh'zīhi",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخِزْيَ",
        "answer": "the disgrace",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-khiz'ya",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَسِرُوا",
        "answer": "(will) lose",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "khasirū",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخُسْرَانُ",
        "answer": "(is) the loss",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "l-khus'rānu",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the losers",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the losers",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirūna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَاسِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the losers",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "l-khāsirīna",
        "frequency": "65",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْشَوْنَ",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "yakhshawna",
        "frequency": "48",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَخْتَصِمُونَ",
        "answer": "will dispute",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "takhtaṣimūna",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) abide eternally",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِدِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) abide eternally",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "khālidīna",
        "frequency": "87",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْخَالِصُ",
        "answer": "the pure",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-khāliṣu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخْلِصًا",
        "answer": "(being) sincere",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "mukh'liṣan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخْلِصًا",
        "answer": "(being) sincere",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "mukh'liṣan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخْلِصًا",
        "answer": "(being) sincere",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "mukh'liṣan",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخْلِفُ",
        "answer": "Allah fails",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yukh'lifu",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْتَلِفُونَ",
        "answer": "differ",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "yakhtalifūna",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْتَلِفُونَ",
        "answer": "differ",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "yakhtalifūna",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُخْتَلِفًا",
        "answer": "(of) different",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "mukh'talifan",
        "frequency": "127",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْلُقُ",
        "answer": "He creates",
        "pcklId": "117",
        "tlit": "yakhluqu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "He created",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَكُمْ",
        "answer": "He created you",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "khalaqakum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَخْلُقُكُمْ",
        "answer": "He creates you",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "yakhluqukum",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلَقَ",
        "answer": "created",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "khalaqa",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقًا",
        "answer": "creation",
        "pcklId": "234",
        "tlit": "khalqan",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَلْقٍ",
        "answer": "creation",
        "pcklId": "235",
        "tlit": "khalqin",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَالِقُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Creator",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "khāliqu",
        "frequency": "261",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخَافُ",
        "answer": "[I] fear",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "tlit": "akhāfu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُخَوِّفُ",
        "answer": "threatens",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "yukhawwifu",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُخَوِّفُونَكَ",
        "answer": "And they threaten you",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "wayukhawwifūnaka",
        "frequency": "124",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوَّلَهُ",
        "answer": "He bestows on him",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "khawwalahu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَوَّلْنَاهُ",
        "answer": "We bestow (on) him",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "khawwalnāhu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "ادْخُلُوا",
        "answer": "Enter",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "ud'khulū",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَادْخُلُوهَا",
        "answer": "so enter it",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "fa-ud'khulūhā",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَعَا",
        "answer": "he calls",
        "pcklId": "118",
        "tlit": "daʿā",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدْعُو",
        "answer": "he used to call",
        "pcklId": "119",
        "tlit": "yadʿū",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَدْعُونَ",
        "answer": "you invoke",
        "pcklId": "120",
        "tlit": "tadʿūna",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "دَعَانَا",
        "answer": "he calls upon Us",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "daʿānā",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "(of) the world",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدُّنْيَا",
        "answer": "world",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "l-dun'yā",
        "frequency": "133",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "107",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "108",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "109",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِ",
        "answer": "besides",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "dūni",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "دُونِهِ",
        "answer": "besides Him",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "dūnihi",
        "frequency": "144",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينَ",
        "answer": "(in) the religion",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "l-dīna",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينُ",
        "answer": "(is) the religion",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-dīnu",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينَ",
        "answer": "(in) the religion",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "l-dīna",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "دِينِي",
        "answer": "(in) my religion",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "dīnī",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُكِرَ",
        "answer": "Allah is mentioned",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "dhukira",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُكِرَ",
        "answer": "are mentioned",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "dhukira",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَذَكَّرُ",
        "answer": "will take heed",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "yatadhakkaru",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَذَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "take heed",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "yatadhakkarūna",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَذِكْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "surely, (is) a reminder",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "ladhik'rā",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرِ",
        "answer": "(the) remembrance of Allah",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "dhik'ri",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذِكْرِ",
        "answer": "(the) remembrance",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "dhik'ri",
        "frequency": "292",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الذُّنُوبَ",
        "answer": "the sins",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-dhunūba",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُوقُوا",
        "answer": "Taste",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "dhūqū",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَذَاقَهُمُ",
        "answer": "So Allah made them",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "fa-adhāqahumu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَ",
        "answer": "you see",
        "pcklId": "183",
        "tlit": "tara",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَتَرَاهُ",
        "answer": "and you see it",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "fatarāhu",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَرَأَيْتُمْ",
        "answer": "Then do you see",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "afara-aytum",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَى",
        "answer": "it sees",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَرَى",
        "answer": "you will see",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "tarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَرَى",
        "answer": "And you will see",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "watarā",
        "frequency": "328",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "704",
        "tlit": "rabbukum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "705",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "706",
        "tlit": "rabbahu",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) his Lord",
        "pcklId": "707",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "708",
        "tlit": "rabbakum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّي",
        "answer": "my Lord",
        "pcklId": "709",
        "tlit": "rabbī",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "710",
        "tlit": "rabbahum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِ",
        "answer": "his Lord",
        "pcklId": "711",
        "tlit": "rabbihi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "712",
        "tlit": "rabbahum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "713",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "714",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "715",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "716",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهَا",
        "answer": "(of) its Lord",
        "pcklId": "717",
        "tlit": "rabbihā",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّكُمْ",
        "answer": "(of) your Lord",
        "pcklId": "718",
        "tlit": "rabbikum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّهُمْ",
        "answer": "their Lord",
        "pcklId": "719",
        "tlit": "rabbahum",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "(of) their Lord",
        "pcklId": "720",
        "tlit": "rabbihim",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "(the) Lord",
        "pcklId": "721",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُرْجَعُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be returned",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "tur'jaʿūna",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْجِعُكُمْ",
        "answer": "(is) your return",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "marjiʿukum",
        "frequency": "104",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَجُلًا",
        "answer": "a man",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "rajulan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَجُلًا",
        "answer": "and a man",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "warajulan",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِرَجُلٍ",
        "answer": "to one man ",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "lirajulin",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَرْجُو",
        "answer": "and hoping",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wayarjū",
        "frequency": "28",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَةَ",
        "answer": "(for the) Mercy",
        "pcklId": "196",
        "tlit": "raḥmata",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَحْمَةٍ",
        "answer": "mercy",
        "pcklId": "197",
        "tlit": "biraḥmatin",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَتِهِ",
        "answer": "(of) His mercy",
        "pcklId": "198",
        "tlit": "raḥmatihi",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَحْمَةِ",
        "answer": "(the) Mercy",
        "pcklId": "199",
        "tlit": "raḥmati",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمُ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "307",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmu",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرِّزْقَ",
        "answer": "the provision",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "l-riz'qa",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُرْسِلُ",
        "answer": "and sends",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "wayur'silu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "رُسُلٌ",
        "answer": "Messengers",
        "pcklId": "380",
        "tlit": "rusulun",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْضَىٰ",
        "answer": "He likes",
        "pcklId": "27",
        "tlit": "yarḍā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرْضَهُ",
        "answer": "He likes it",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "yarḍahu",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَ",
        "answer": "Allah (had) intended",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "arāda",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَنِيَ",
        "answer": "Allah intended for me",
        "pcklId": "127",
        "tlit": "arādaniya",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَادَنِي",
        "answer": "if He intended for me",
        "pcklId": "128",
        "tlit": "arādanī",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَرْعًا",
        "answer": "crops",
        "pcklId": "10",
        "tlit": "zarʿan",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "زُلْفَىٰ",
        "answer": "(in) nearness",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "zul'fā",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "زُمَرًا",
        "answer": "(in) groups",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "zumaran",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "زُمَرًا",
        "answer": "(in) groups",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "zumaran",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَوْجَهَا",
        "answer": "its mate",
        "pcklId": "59",
        "tlit": "zawjahā",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزْوَاجٍ",
        "answer": "kinds",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "azwājin",
        "frequency": "81",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَأَلْتَهُمْ",
        "answer": "you ask them",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "sa-altahum",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُسَبِّحُونَ",
        "answer": "glorifying",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yusabbiḥūna",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَهُ",
        "answer": "Glory be to Him",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥānahu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُبْحَانَهُ",
        "answer": "Glory be to Him",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "sub'ḥānahu",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِهِ",
        "answer": "His Path",
        "pcklId": "142",
        "tlit": "sabīlihi",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاجِدًا",
        "answer": "prostrating",
        "pcklId": "86",
        "tlit": "sājidan",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسَخَّرَ",
        "answer": "And He subjected",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wasakhara",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّاخِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the mockers",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "tlit": "l-sākhirīna",
        "frequency": "42",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْرَفُوا",
        "answer": "have transgressed",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "asrafū",
        "frequency": "23",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَسَلَكَهُ",
        "answer": "and He makes it flow",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "fasalakahu",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَسْلِمُوا",
        "answer": "and submit",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "wa-aslimū",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَامٌ",
        "answer": "Peace be",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "salāmun",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَلَمًا",
        "answer": "(belonging) exclusively",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "salaman",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْإِسْلَامِ",
        "answer": "for Islam",
        "pcklId": "93",
        "tlit": "lil'is'lāmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْلِمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who submit",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "l-mus'limīna",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَمِعُونَ",
        "answer": "they listen (to)",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "yastamiʿūna",
        "frequency": "185",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاءِ",
        "answer": "the sky",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "l-samāi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "(of) the heavens",
        "pcklId": "258",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالسَّمَاوَاتُ",
        "answer": "and the heavens",
        "pcklId": "259",
        "tlit": "wal-samāwātu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "260",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسَمًّى",
        "answer": "specified",
        "pcklId": "371",
        "tlit": "musamman",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسَمًّى",
        "answer": "specified",
        "pcklId": "372",
        "tlit": "musamman",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَسْوَأَ",
        "answer": "(the) worst",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "aswa-a",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُوءَ",
        "answer": "(the) worst",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "sūa",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "سُوءِ",
        "answer": "(the) evil",
        "pcklId": "81",
        "tlit": "sūi",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "السُّوءُ",
        "answer": "the evil",
        "pcklId": "82",
        "tlit": "l-sūu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَاتُ",
        "answer": "(the) evils",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "sayyiātu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَاتُ",
        "answer": "(the) evils",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "tlit": "sayyiātu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيِّئَاتُ",
        "answer": "(the) evils",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "sayyiātu",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُسْوَدَّةٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) blackened",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "mus'waddatun",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسِيقَ",
        "answer": "And (will) be driven",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wasīqa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَسِيقَ",
        "answer": "And (will) be driven",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wasīqa",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَوِي",
        "answer": "equal",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "yastawī",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَوِيَانِ",
        "answer": "they both equal",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "yastawiyāni",
        "frequency": "83",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَشَابِهًا",
        "answer": "(its parts) resembling each other",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "mutashābihan",
        "frequency": "12",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَرَحَ",
        "answer": "Allah has expanded",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "sharaḥa",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَشْرَقَتِ",
        "answer": "And (will) shine",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "wa-ashraqati",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْرَكْتَ",
        "answer": "you associate (with Allah)",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "ashrakta",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "they associate (with Him)",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "yush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُرَكَاءُ",
        "answer": "partners",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "shurakāu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشْعُرُونَ",
        "answer": "they perceive",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "yashʿurūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْعُرُونَ",
        "answer": "perceive",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "tashʿurūna",
        "frequency": "40",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّفَاعَةُ",
        "answer": "the intercession",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "l-shafāʿatu",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "شُفَعَاءَ",
        "answer": "intercessors",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "shufaʿāa",
        "frequency": "31",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَشْكُرُوا",
        "answer": "you are grateful",
        "pcklId": "39",
        "tlit": "tashkurū",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّاكِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the thankful ones",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "tlit": "l-shākirīna",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتَشَاكِسُونَ",
        "answer": "quarreling",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "mutashākisūna",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "اشْمَأَزَّتْ",
        "answer": "shrink with aversion",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ish'ma-azzat",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "الشَّمْسَ",
        "answer": "the sun",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-shamsa",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشَّهَادَةِ",
        "answer": "and the witnessed",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "wal-shahādati",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالشُّهَدَاءِ",
        "answer": "and the witnesses",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "wal-shuhadāi",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He willed",
        "pcklId": "175",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "شِئْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you will",
        "pcklId": "176",
        "tlit": "shi'tum",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "177",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُونَ",
        "answer": "they wish",
        "pcklId": "178",
        "tlit": "yashāūna",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "He wills",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "yashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَاءَ",
        "answer": "Allah wills",
        "pcklId": "180",
        "tlit": "shāa",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَشَاءُ",
        "answer": "we wish",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "nashāu",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْئًا",
        "answer": "anything",
        "pcklId": "449",
        "tlit": "shayan",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "things",
        "pcklId": "450",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "شَيْءٍ",
        "answer": "things",
        "pcklId": "451",
        "tlit": "shayin",
        "frequency": "519",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصَّابِرُونَ",
        "answer": "the patient ones",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "l-ṣābirūna",
        "frequency": "103",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَصْحَابِ",
        "answer": "(the) companions",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "aṣḥābi",
        "frequency": "97",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّدُورِ",
        "answer": "of what (is) in the breasts",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "l-ṣudūri",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدْرَهُ",
        "answer": "his breast",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "ṣadrahu",
        "frequency": "46",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَدَقَنَا",
        "answer": "has fulfilled for us",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "ṣadaqanā",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَصَدَّقَ",
        "answer": "and believed",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "waṣaddaqa",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالصِّدْقِ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "bil-ṣid'qi",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالصِّدْقِ",
        "answer": "the truth",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "bil-ṣid'qi",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُصْرَفُونَ",
        "answer": "are you turning away",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "tuṣ'rafūna",
        "frequency": "30",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَصَعِقَ",
        "answer": "then (will) fall dead",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "faṣaʿiqa",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصْفَرًّا",
        "answer": "turn yellow",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "muṣ'farran",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَاصْطَفَىٰ",
        "answer": "surely, He (could) have chosen",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "la-iṣ'ṭafā",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصَابَهُمْ",
        "answer": "Then struck them",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣābahum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَيُصِيبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "will strike them",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "sayuṣībuhum",
        "frequency": "77",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصُّورِ",
        "answer": "the trumpet",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-ṣūri",
        "frequency": "19",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرَبْنَا",
        "answer": "We have set forth",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "ḍarabnā",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَرَبَ",
        "answer": "Allah sets forth",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "ḍaraba",
        "frequency": "58",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضُرٌّ",
        "answer": "adversity",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ḍurrun",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِضُرٍّ",
        "answer": "harm",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "biḍurrin",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضُرِّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) harm (from) Him",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "ḍurrihi",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضُرٌّ",
        "answer": "adversity",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "ḍurrun",
        "frequency": "74",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَّ",
        "answer": "goes astray",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "ḍalla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَضِلُّ",
        "answer": "he strays",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yaḍillu",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُضِلَّ",
        "answer": "to mislead",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "liyuḍilla",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضْلِلِ",
        "answer": "Allah lets go astray",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "yuḍ'lili",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُضْلِلِ",
        "answer": "Allah lets go astray ",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "yuḍ'lili",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "ضَلَالٍ",
        "answer": "error",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "tlit": "ḍalālin",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُضِلٍّ",
        "answer": "misleader",
        "pcklId": "190",
        "tlit": "muḍillin",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الطَّاغُوتَ",
        "answer": "the false gods",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-ṭāghūta",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَطْوِيَّاتٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) folded",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "maṭwiyyātun",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "طِبْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you have done well",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "ṭib'tum",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلَلٌ",
        "answer": "coverings",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ẓulalun",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلَلٌ",
        "answer": "coverings",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "ẓulalun",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "did wrong",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "ẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَلَمُوا",
        "answer": "have wronged",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "ẓalamū",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُظْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "will not be wronged",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "yuẓ'lamūna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَظْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) more unjust",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "aẓlamu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظُلُمَاتٍ",
        "answer": "darkness[es]",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "ẓulumātin",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "to the wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "tlit": "lilẓẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْبُدِ",
        "answer": "so worship",
        "pcklId": "95",
        "tlit": "fa-uʿ'budi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعْبُدُهُمْ",
        "answer": "we worship them",
        "pcklId": "96",
        "tlit": "naʿbuduhum",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْبُدَ",
        "answer": "I worship",
        "pcklId": "97",
        "tlit": "aʿbuda",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْبُدُ",
        "answer": "I worship Allah",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "aʿbudu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْبُدُوا",
        "answer": "So worship",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "fa-uʿ'budū",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْبُدُوهَا",
        "answer": "they worship them",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "yaʿbudūhā",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْبُدُ",
        "answer": "(to) worship",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "aʿbudu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاعْبُدْ",
        "answer": "But worship Allah",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "fa-uʿ'bud",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِعِبَادِهِ",
        "answer": "in His slaves",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "liʿibādihi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا عِبَادِ",
        "answer": "O My slaves",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "yāʿibādi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادَهُ",
        "answer": "His slaves",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "ʿibādahu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا عِبَادِ",
        "answer": "O My slaves",
        "pcklId": "228",
        "tlit": "yāʿibādi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِ",
        "answer": "(to) My slaves",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "ʿibādi",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَبْدَهُ",
        "answer": "(for) His slave",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "ʿabdahu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِبَادِكَ",
        "answer": "Your slaves",
        "pcklId": "231",
        "tlit": "ʿibādika",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا عِبَادِيَ",
        "answer": "O My slaves",
        "pcklId": "232",
        "tlit": "yāʿibādiya",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمُعْجِزِينَ",
        "answer": "will be able to escape",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "bimuʿ'jizīna",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابَ",
        "answer": "(the) punishment",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the punishment",
        "pcklId": "268",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "punishment",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابُ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "270",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَعَذَابُ",
        "answer": "and certainly (the) punishment",
        "pcklId": "271",
        "tlit": "walaʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٌ",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābun",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the punishment",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابُ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابُ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābu",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابَ",
        "answer": "the punishment",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhāba",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَذَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) punishment",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "l-ʿadhābi",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَرَبِيًّا",
        "answer": "(in) Arabic",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "ʿarabiyyan",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَرْشِ",
        "answer": "the Throne",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "tlit": "l-ʿarshi",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِعَزِيزٍ",
        "answer": "All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "biʿazīzin",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزِ",
        "answer": "the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzi",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَصَيْتُ",
        "answer": "I disobey",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "ʿaṣaytu",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَظِيمٍ",
        "answer": "great",
        "pcklId": "85",
        "tlit": "ʿaẓīmin",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْقِلُونَ",
        "answer": "they understand",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "yaʿqilūna",
        "frequency": "49",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "300",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "301",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "knew",
        "pcklId": "302",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "303",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you will know",
        "pcklId": "304",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "305",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْلَمُوا",
        "answer": "they know",
        "pcklId": "306",
        "tlit": "yaʿlamū",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is the) Best-Knower",
        "pcklId": "448",
        "tlit": "aʿlamu",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the worlds",
        "pcklId": "533",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِلْمٍ",
        "answer": "knowledge",
        "pcklId": "634",
        "tlit": "ʿil'min",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَلِيمٌ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Knower",
        "pcklId": "809",
        "tlit": "ʿalīmun",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَالِمَ",
        "answer": "Knower",
        "pcklId": "837",
        "tlit": "ʿālima",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتَعَالَىٰ",
        "answer": "And High is He",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "wataʿālā",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "taʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِلُوا",
        "answer": "they did",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "ʿamilū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلُونَ",
        "answer": "do",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "yaʿmalūna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "اعْمَلُوا",
        "answer": "Work",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "iʿ'malū",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمِلَتْ",
        "answer": "it did",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "ʿamilat",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَمَلُكَ",
        "answer": "your deeds",
        "pcklId": "326",
        "tlit": "ʿamaluka",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَامِلٌ",
        "answer": "working",
        "pcklId": "356",
        "tlit": "ʿāmilun",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَامِلِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the workers",
        "pcklId": "357",
        "tlit": "l-ʿāmilīna",
        "frequency": "360",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "34"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِوَجٍ",
        "answer": "crookedness",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "ʿiwajin",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُرَفٌ",
        "answer": "(are) lofty mansions",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ghurafun",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "غُرَفٌ",
        "answer": "lofty mansions",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "ghurafun",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَغْفِرُ",
        "answer": "forgives",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "yaghfiru",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَفَّارُ",
        "answer": "the Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "l-ghafāru",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَفُورُ",
        "answer": "(is) the Oft-Forgiving",
        "pcklId": "163",
        "tlit": "l-ghafūru",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَغْنَىٰ",
        "answer": "avail",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "aghnā",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَنِيٌّ",
        "answer": "(is) free from need",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "ghaniyyun",
        "frequency": "73",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْغَيْبِ",
        "answer": "(of) the unseen",
        "pcklId": "38",
        "tlit": "l-ghaybi",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِغَيْرِ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "124",
        "tlit": "bighayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرَ",
        "answer": "without",
        "pcklId": "125",
        "tlit": "ghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَفَغَيْرَ",
        "answer": "Is (it) other than",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "afaghayra",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "فُتِحَتْ",
        "answer": "(will) be opened",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "futiḥat",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفُتِحَتْ",
        "answer": "and (will) be opened",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wafutiḥat",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "فِتْنَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a trial",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "fit'natun",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَافْتَدَوْا",
        "answer": "they would ransom",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "la-if'tadaw",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَرَّطْتُ",
        "answer": "I neglected",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "farraṭtu",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاطِرَ",
        "answer": "Creator",
        "pcklId": "17",
        "tlit": "fāṭira",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَفْعَلُونَ",
        "answer": "they do",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "yafʿalūna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَفَكَّرُونَ",
        "answer": "who ponder",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "yatafakkarūna",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِمَفَازَتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "to their place of salvation",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "tlit": "bimafāzatihim",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقِهِمْ",
        "answer": "above them",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "fawqihim",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَوْقِهَا",
        "answer": "above them",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "fawqihā",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْضَتُهُ",
        "answer": "(will be) in His Grip",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "qabḍatuhu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلُ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "qablu",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "(were) before them",
        "pcklId": "185",
        "tlit": "qablihim",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِهِمْ",
        "answer": "before them",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "tlit": "qablihim",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "187",
        "tlit": "qabli",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِ",
        "answer": "before",
        "pcklId": "188",
        "tlit": "qabli",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَبْلِكَ",
        "answer": "(were) before you",
        "pcklId": "189",
        "tlit": "qablika",
        "frequency": "294",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَقْدِرُ",
        "answer": "and restricts",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wayaqdiru",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدَرُوا",
        "answer": "they appraised",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "qadarū",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَدْرِهِ",
        "answer": "appraisal",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "qadrihi",
        "frequency": "132",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقُرْآنِ",
        "answer": "Quran",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "l-qur'āni",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُرْآنًا",
        "answer": "A Quran",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "qur'ānan",
        "frequency": "88",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُقَرِّبُونَا",
        "answer": "that they may bring us near",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "liyuqarribūnā",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْقَاسِيَةِ",
        "answer": "to (those are) hardened",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "lil'qāsiyati",
        "frequency": "7",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْشَعِرُّ",
        "answer": "Shiver",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "taqshaʿirru",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَضَىٰ",
        "answer": "He has decreed",
        "pcklId": "43",
        "tlit": "qaḍā",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُضِيَ",
        "answer": "and it (will) be judged",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "waquḍiya",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُضِيَ",
        "answer": "And (will) be judged",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "waquḍiya",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "qulūbuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقُلُوبُهُمْ",
        "answer": "and their hearts",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "waqulūbuhum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبُ",
        "answer": "(the) hearts",
        "pcklId": "123",
        "tlit": "qulūbu",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَقَالِيدُ",
        "answer": "(are the) keys",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "maqālīdu",
        "frequency": "4",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَلِيلًا",
        "answer": "(for) a little",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "qalīlan",
        "frequency": "76",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَالْقَمَرَ",
        "answer": "and the moon",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wal-qamara",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَانِتٌ",
        "answer": "(is) devoutly obedient ",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "qānitun",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقْنَطُوا",
        "answer": "despair",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "taqnaṭū",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَهَّارُ",
        "answer": "the Irresistible",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "l-qahāru",
        "frequency": "10",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1345",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1346",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1347",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1348",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1349",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1350",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1351",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقِيلَ",
        "answer": "And it will be said",
        "pcklId": "1352",
        "tlit": "waqīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَيَقُولُنَّ",
        "answer": "Surely, they will say",
        "pcklId": "1353",
        "tlit": "layaqūlunna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1354",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1355",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1356",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1357",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1358",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلِ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1359",
        "tlit": "quli",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "he says",
        "pcklId": "1360",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَهَا",
        "answer": "said it",
        "pcklId": "1361",
        "tlit": "qālahā",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1362",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولَ",
        "answer": "should say",
        "pcklId": "1363",
        "tlit": "taqūla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولَ",
        "answer": "it should say",
        "pcklId": "1364",
        "tlit": "taqūla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولَ",
        "answer": "it should say",
        "pcklId": "1365",
        "tlit": "taqūla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلْ",
        "answer": "Say",
        "pcklId": "1366",
        "tlit": "qul",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "64"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "and (will) say",
        "pcklId": "1367",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "They (will) say",
        "pcklId": "1368",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيلَ",
        "answer": "It will be said",
        "pcklId": "1369",
        "tlit": "qīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "and (will) say",
        "pcklId": "1370",
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالُوا",
        "answer": "And they will say",
        "pcklId": "1371",
        "tlit": "waqālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقِيلَ",
        "answer": "and it will be said",
        "pcklId": "1372",
        "tlit": "waqīla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْلَ",
        "answer": "the Word",
        "pcklId": "1694",
        "tlit": "l-qawla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "412",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "413",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "for a people",
        "pcklId": "414",
        "tlit": "liqawmin",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "52"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "542",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "543",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "544",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "545",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "546",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقِيَامَةِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Resurrection",
        "pcklId": "547",
        "tlit": "l-qiyāmati",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَائِمًا",
        "answer": "and standing",
        "pcklId": "595",
        "tlit": "waqāiman",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "قِيَامٌ",
        "answer": "(will be) standing",
        "pcklId": "596",
        "tlit": "qiyāmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُقِيمٌ",
        "answer": "everlasting",
        "pcklId": "616",
        "tlit": "muqīmun",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "40"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسْتَكْبَرْتَ",
        "answer": "and were arrogant",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "wa-is'takbarta",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْبَرُ",
        "answer": "(is) greater",
        "pcklId": "75",
        "tlit": "akbaru",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُتَكَبِّرِينَ",
        "answer": "for the arrogant",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "lil'mutakabbirīna",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَكَبِّرِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) the arrogant",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "l-mutakabirīna",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "72"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Book",
        "pcklId": "253",
        "tlit": "l-kitābi",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "254",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "كِتَابًا",
        "answer": "a Book",
        "pcklId": "255",
        "tlit": "kitāban",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابَ",
        "answer": "the Book",
        "pcklId": "256",
        "tlit": "l-kitāba",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكِتَابُ",
        "answer": "the Record",
        "pcklId": "257",
        "tlit": "l-kitābu",
        "frequency": "319",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرُهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "aktharuhum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكْثَرَهُمْ",
        "answer": "most of them",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "aktharahum",
        "frequency": "167",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَبَ",
        "answer": "lies",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "kadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَبُوا",
        "answer": "lied",
        "pcklId": "9",
        "tlit": "kadhabū",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "Denied",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "kadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَذَّبَ",
        "answer": "and denies",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "wakadhaba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَكَذَّبْتَ",
        "answer": "but you denied",
        "pcklId": "116",
        "tlit": "fakadhabta",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَاذِبٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a liar",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "kādhibun",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرَّةً",
        "answer": "another chance",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "karratan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "earn",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "taksibūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبُوا",
        "answer": "they earned",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "kasabū",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكْسِبُونَ",
        "answer": "earn",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "yaksibūna",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبُوا",
        "answer": "they earned",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "kasabū",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَسَبُوا",
        "answer": "they earned",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "kasabū",
        "frequency": "67",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "51"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَاشِفَاتُ",
        "answer": "removers",
        "pcklId": "18",
        "tlit": "kāshifātu",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَكْفُرُوا",
        "answer": "you disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "takfurū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "63"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَرُوا",
        "answer": "disbelieve",
        "pcklId": "219",
        "tlit": "kafarū",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُكَفِّرَ",
        "answer": "That Allah will remove",
        "pcklId": "297",
        "tlit": "liyukaffira",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَفَّارٌ",
        "answer": "and a disbeliever",
        "pcklId": "333",
        "tlit": "kaffārun",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكُفْرَ",
        "answer": "ungratefulness",
        "pcklId": "375",
        "tlit": "l-kuf'ra",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكُفْرِكَ",
        "answer": "in your disbelief",
        "pcklId": "376",
        "tlit": "bikuf'rika",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "for the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "482",
        "tlit": "lil'kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "483",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرِينَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "484",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirīna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِكَافٍ",
        "answer": "sufficient",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "bikāfin",
        "frequency": "33",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلٌّ",
        "answer": "each",
        "pcklId": "276",
        "tlit": "kullun",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "(of) all",
        "pcklId": "278",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّ",
        "answer": "all",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "kulli",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلُّ",
        "answer": "every",
        "pcklId": "280",
        "tlit": "kullu",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلِمَةُ",
        "answer": "the word",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "kalimatu",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَلِمَةُ",
        "answer": "(the) word",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "kalimatu",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَوِّرُ",
        "answer": "He wraps",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yukawwiru",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُكَوِّرُ",
        "answer": "and wraps",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "wayukawwiru",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "1092",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانَ",
        "answer": "he used to call",
        "pcklId": "1093",
        "tlit": "kāna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَكُونَ",
        "answer": "I be",
        "pcklId": "1094",
        "tlit": "akūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you used to",
        "pcklId": "1095",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they",
        "pcklId": "1096",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "26"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "1097",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "35"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they were",
        "pcklId": "1098",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "1099",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "46"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَكُونُوا",
        "answer": "they had",
        "pcklId": "1100",
        "tlit": "yakūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "1101",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَانُوا",
        "answer": "they used to",
        "pcklId": "1102",
        "tlit": "kānū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُ",
        "answer": "I was",
        "pcklId": "1103",
        "tlit": "kuntu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "لَكُنْتُ",
        "answer": "surely, I (would) have been",
        "pcklId": "1104",
        "tlit": "lakuntu",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَكُونَ",
        "answer": "then I could be",
        "pcklId": "1105",
        "tlit": "fa-akūna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "58"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنْتَ",
        "answer": "and you were",
        "pcklId": "1106",
        "tlit": "wakunta",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "59"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَتَكُونَنَّ",
        "answer": "and you will surely be",
        "pcklId": "1107",
        "tlit": "walatakūnanna",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكُنْ",
        "answer": "and be",
        "pcklId": "1108",
        "tlit": "wakun",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "66"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَكَانَتِكُمْ",
        "answer": "your position",
        "pcklId": "1389",
        "tlit": "makānatikum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "39"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَلْبَابِ",
        "answer": "those of understanding",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "l-albābi",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَلْبَابِ",
        "answer": "the men of understanding",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "l-albābi",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَلْبَابِ",
        "answer": "for those of understanding",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "l-albābi",
        "frequency": "16",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَاءَ",
        "answer": "(of the) meeting",
        "pcklId": "129",
        "tlit": "liqāa",
        "frequency": "146",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلْوَانُهُ",
        "answer": "colors",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "alwānuhu",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Is (there) not",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "alaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "32"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Is not",
        "pcklId": "67",
        "tlit": "alaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Is not",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "alaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلَيْسَ",
        "answer": "Is (there) not",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "alaysa",
        "frequency": "89",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلَ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "53",
        "tlit": "al-layla",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "the night",
        "pcklId": "54",
        "tlit": "al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّيْلِ",
        "answer": "(of) the night",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "al-layli",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَلِينُ",
        "answer": "relax",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "talīnu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمَتَّعْ",
        "answer": "Enjoy",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "tamattaʿ",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمِثْلَهُ",
        "answer": "and (the) like of it",
        "pcklId": "64",
        "tlit": "wamith'lahu",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلٍ",
        "answer": "example",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "mathalin",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلًا",
        "answer": "an example ",
        "pcklId": "140",
        "tlit": "mathalan",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَثَلًا",
        "answer": "(in) comparison",
        "pcklId": "141",
        "tlit": "mathalan",
        "frequency": "169",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "29"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَّ",
        "answer": "touches",
        "pcklId": "46",
        "tlit": "massa",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَسَّ",
        "answer": "touches",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "massa",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمَسُّهُمُ",
        "answer": "will touch them",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "yamassuhumu",
        "frequency": "61",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُمْسِكُ",
        "answer": "Then He keeps",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "fayum'siku",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُمْسِكَاتُ",
        "answer": "withholders",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "mum'sikātu",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَمْلِكُونَ",
        "answer": "possessing",
        "pcklId": "35",
        "tlit": "yamlikūna",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "43"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(is) the dominion",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُلْكُ",
        "answer": "(is the) dominion",
        "pcklId": "80",
        "tlit": "mul'ku",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "44"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَلَائِكَةَ",
        "answer": "the Angels",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "l-malāikata",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "75"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَمُتْ",
        "answer": "die",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "tamut",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَوْتِهَا",
        "answer": "(of) their death",
        "pcklId": "101",
        "tlit": "mawtihā",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَوْتَ",
        "answer": "the death",
        "pcklId": "102",
        "tlit": "l-mawta",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَيِّتٌ",
        "answer": "will die",
        "pcklId": "149",
        "tlit": "mayyitun",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَيِّتُونَ",
        "answer": "(will also) die",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "mayyitūna",
        "frequency": "165",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "30"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَاءً",
        "answer": "water",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "māan",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَيُنَبِّئُكُمْ",
        "answer": "then He will inform you",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "fayunabbi-ukum",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالنَّبِيِّينَ",
        "answer": "the Prophets",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "bil-nabiyīna",
        "frequency": "160",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنَابِيعَ",
        "answer": "(as) springs",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "yanābīʿa",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُنَجِّي",
        "answer": "And Allah will deliver",
        "pcklId": "33",
        "tlit": "wayunajjī",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْدَادًا",
        "answer": "rivals",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "andādan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُنْذِرُونَكُمْ",
        "answer": "and warning you",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "wayundhirūnakum",
        "frequency": "130",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَزَّلَ",
        "answer": "has revealed",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "nazzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "[We] have revealed",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "And He sent down",
        "pcklId": "224",
        "tlit": "wa-anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلَ",
        "answer": "sends down",
        "pcklId": "225",
        "tlit": "anzala",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْزَلْنَا",
        "answer": "We revealed",
        "pcklId": "226",
        "tlit": "anzalnā",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُنْزِلَ",
        "answer": "is revealed",
        "pcklId": "227",
        "tlit": "unzila",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "55"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَنْزِيلُ",
        "answer": "(The) revelation",
        "pcklId": "275",
        "tlit": "tanzīlu",
        "frequency": "293",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسِيَ",
        "answer": "he forgets",
        "pcklId": "29",
        "tlit": "nasiya",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْصَرُونَ",
        "answer": "you will be helped",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "tunṣarūna",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَنْظُرُونَ",
        "answer": "waiting",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "yanẓurūna",
        "frequency": "129",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَنِعْمَ",
        "answer": "So excellent",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "faniʿ'ma",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْعَامِ",
        "answer": "the cattle",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "l-anʿāmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَةً",
        "answer": "a favor",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "niʿ'matan",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "نِعْمَةً",
        "answer": "a favor",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "niʿ'matan",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "49"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَنُفِخَ",
        "answer": "And (will) be blown",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "wanufikha",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُفِخَ",
        "answer": "(it will) be blown",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "nufikha",
        "frequency": "20",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "68"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "a soul",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسَهُمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "245",
        "tlit": "anfusahum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَلِنَفْسِهِ",
        "answer": "then (it is) for his soul",
        "pcklId": "246",
        "tlit": "falinafsihi",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْفُسَ",
        "answer": "the souls",
        "pcklId": "247",
        "tlit": "l-anfusa",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْفُسِهِمْ",
        "answer": "themselves",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "anfusihim",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "53"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٌ",
        "answer": "a soul",
        "pcklId": "249",
        "tlit": "nafsun",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "56"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَفْسٍ",
        "answer": "soul",
        "pcklId": "250",
        "tlit": "nafsin",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْقِذُ",
        "answer": "save",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "tunqidhu",
        "frequency": "5",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "انْتِقَامٍ",
        "answer": "All-Able of retribution",
        "pcklId": "13",
        "tlit": "intiqāmin",
        "frequency": "17",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّهَارِ",
        "answer": "the day",
        "pcklId": "44",
        "tlit": "l-nahāri",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّهَارَ",
        "answer": "the day",
        "pcklId": "45",
        "tlit": "l-nahāra",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنَابُوا",
        "answer": "and turn",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "wa-anābū",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "17"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنِيبُوا",
        "answer": "And turn",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "wa-anībū",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "54"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُنِيبًا",
        "answer": "turning",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "munīban",
        "frequency": "18",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "(of) the Fire",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "99",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّارِ",
        "answer": "the Fire",
        "pcklId": "100",
        "tlit": "l-nāri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "19"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُورٍ",
        "answer": "a light",
        "pcklId": "172",
        "tlit": "nūrin",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِنُورِ",
        "answer": "with (the) light",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "binūri",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for people",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "27"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلنَّاسِ",
        "answer": "for [the] mankind",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "lilnnāsi",
        "frequency": "241",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَنَامِهَا",
        "answer": "their sleep",
        "pcklId": "3",
        "tlit": "manāmihā",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "110",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَاهُمُ",
        "answer": "Allah has guided them",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "hadāhumu",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "18"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "He guides",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِ",
        "answer": "Allah guides",
        "pcklId": "113",
        "tlit": "yahdi",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "37"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَدَانِي",
        "answer": "(had) guided me",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "hadānī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "اهْتَدَىٰ",
        "answer": "accepts guidance",
        "pcklId": "179",
        "tlit": "ih'tadā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "هُدَى",
        "answer": "(is the) guidance",
        "pcklId": "267",
        "tlit": "hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَادٍ",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "289",
        "tlit": "hādin",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "23"
    },
    {
        "question": "هَادٍ",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "290",
        "tlit": "hādin",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "36"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَسْتَهْزِئُونَ",
        "answer": "mock",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "yastahziūna",
        "frequency": "34",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "48"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهِيجُ",
        "answer": "they wither",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yahīju",
        "frequency": "2",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "21"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِوَجْهِهِ",
        "answer": "with his face",
        "pcklId": "55",
        "tlit": "biwajhihi",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "وُجُوهُهُمْ",
        "answer": "their faces",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "wujūhuhum",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْوَاحِدُ",
        "answer": "the One",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "l-wāḥidu",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاحِدَةٍ",
        "answer": "single",
        "pcklId": "47",
        "tlit": "wāḥidatin",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَحْدَهُ",
        "answer": "Alone",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "waḥdahu",
        "frequency": "68",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "45"
    },
    {
        "question": "أُوحِيَ",
        "answer": "it has been revealed",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "ūḥiya",
        "frequency": "78",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "65"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَوْرَثَنَا",
        "answer": "and has made us inherit",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "tlit": "wa-awrathanā",
        "frequency": "35",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَزِرُ",
        "answer": "will bear",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "taziru",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وِزْرَ",
        "answer": "(the) burden",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "wiz'ra",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَازِرَةٌ",
        "answer": "bearer of burdens",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "wāziratun",
        "frequency": "27",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاسِعَةٌ",
        "answer": "(is) spacious",
        "pcklId": "28",
        "tlit": "wāsiʿatun",
        "frequency": "32",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَوُضِعَ",
        "answer": "and (will) be placed",
        "pcklId": "12",
        "tlit": "wawuḍiʿa",
        "frequency": "26",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "69"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمِيعَادَ",
        "answer": "(in His) promise",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-mīʿāda",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدَ",
        "answer": "(The) Promise",
        "pcklId": "135",
        "tlit": "waʿda",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَعْدَهُ",
        "answer": "His promise",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "waʿdahu",
        "frequency": "151",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "74"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُوَفَّى",
        "answer": "will be paid back in full",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "yuwaffā",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَوُفِّيَتْ",
        "answer": "And (will) be paid in full",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "wawuffiyat",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "70"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَفَّى",
        "answer": "takes",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "yatawaffā",
        "frequency": "66",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "42"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقُوا",
        "answer": "Fear",
        "pcklId": "153",
        "tlit": "ittaqū",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَاتَّقُونِ",
        "answer": "So fear Me",
        "pcklId": "154",
        "tlit": "fa-ittaqūni",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقَوْا",
        "answer": "fear",
        "pcklId": "155",
        "tlit": "ittaqaw",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "20"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّقِي",
        "answer": "will shield",
        "pcklId": "156",
        "tlit": "yattaqī",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "(become) righteous",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "yattaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "28"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقَوْا",
        "answer": "feared (Him)",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "ittaqaw",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "61"
    },
    {
        "question": "اتَّقَوْا",
        "answer": "feared",
        "pcklId": "159",
        "tlit": "ittaqaw",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "73"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَّقُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) the righteous",
        "pcklId": "243",
        "tlit": "l-mutaqūna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "33"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَّقِينَ",
        "answer": "the righteous",
        "pcklId": "244",
        "tlit": "l-mutaqīna",
        "frequency": "258",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "57"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَتَوَكَّلُ",
        "answer": "put trust",
        "pcklId": "34",
        "tlit": "yatawakkalu",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِوَكِيلٍ",
        "answer": "a manager",
        "pcklId": "62",
        "tlit": "biwakīlin",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكِيلٌ",
        "answer": "a Guardian",
        "pcklId": "63",
        "tlit": "wakīlun",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "62"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُتَوَكِّلُونَ",
        "answer": "those who trust",
        "pcklId": "69",
        "tlit": "l-mutawakilūna",
        "frequency": "70",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "38"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَلَدًا",
        "answer": "a son",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "waladan",
        "frequency": "102",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْلِيَاءَ",
        "answer": "protectors",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "awliyāa",
        "frequency": "232",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِيَمِينِهِ",
        "answer": "in His Right Hand",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "biyamīnihi",
        "frequency": "71",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a Day",
        "pcklId": "206",
        "tlit": "yawmin",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "207",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "15"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "208",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "24"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "209",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "210",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "47"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَوْمَ",
        "answer": "And (on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "211",
        "tlit": "wayawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "60"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمَ",
        "answer": "(on the) Day",
        "pcklId": "212",
        "tlit": "yawma",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "67"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِكُمْ",
        "answer": "(of) your Day",
        "pcklId": "213",
        "tlit": "yawmikum",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "39",
        "ayah": "71"
    }
]; 
export default words;